[Music]
what's new in Shopify in 2024 release
Wave 2 the Shopify connector allows you
to synchronize data such as items
inventory and customers between Shopify
and business Central and helps you
manage your online store Shopify allows
you to add customer fields or meta
fields to main entities like products or
variants now you can import or export
meta Fields linked to products or
variants in Shopify and use them to do
custom mappings you you can also
synchronize translations with a new
languages action just import languages
from Shopify and add them to items in
business Central your Shopify store then
has the option to change the language of
product descriptions so you can stay
competitive in different markets with
Shopify you can use company cataloges
and business Central to synchronize
company specific prices and discounts
this ensures that each company sees
their negotiated prices and discounts
when they log into your Shopify store
you can also assign specific discounts
to individual customers in business
Central and then create customer
specific orders in Shopify ensuring
personalized pricing you can now map
shipping fee information from Shopify to
business Central more accurately and
with more flexibility when you
synchronize data with Shopify choose
from different types of shipping charges
such as item or item charge and specify
the shipping agent and shipping agent
service you can then make sales orders
with business Central and see see the
shipping charges and shipment methods
such as agent and agent service directly
in your sales documents we've also added
a new way to reconcile transactions with
different payment methods like gift
cards and credit cards you can now post
receipt journals and then reconcile your
transactions directly in business
Central and finally you can now easily
synchronize posted sales invoices to
Shopify you can use the filters and
select to post the invoices for specific
customers and companies
you can then see the orders in Shopify
and see the details of all their orders
like the payment and fulfillment status
thank you for watching